Hey, don't you think we're a bit far out?
No point in searching
if we're not spread out.
Why did I get stuck with you?
Wait, Marlo... You just wanted
alone time with me, didn't you?
Hitch... I'm sorry, but you're
not my first choice either.
Oh, is that right? Well, good for you.
But, don't you think it's odd?
Why would the Scouts kill
a civilian and run for the hills?
They're the same group
that's always risking
their lives for the
sake of humanity.
I can't believe you... Did you forget?
Remember what they did
to Stohess District?
How they turned it into a battlefield?
All those corpses we had to carry?
And how Annie's still missing?
All of her junk is still in
my room... and it's annoying.
But they also uncovered that Titan in
hiding and somehow managed to capture it.
You think any other
regiment could do that?
If the Scouts get disbanded
like this, humanity can't...
Quiet.
I hear water.
Don't move!
Slowly turn this way.
You must be a scout.
Just like that... Not a word.
Now listen to me and do as I...
That's right... Hand over your
guns to the one in front.
And not a word, right?
"Trust"
"Capital Mitras"
Sorry to keep you waiting, Erwin.
I know it's sudden, but let's get
the interrogation over with.
So, it's unmistakable that the Scout
Regiment murdered a civilian?
Judging by the evidence, at least.
Having said that, we can't say
for sure at the time being.
Are you saying the Interior Police are
responsible for issuing the search...?
Hey, Peaure!
Sorry about him, Commander Dawk.
He's still a rookie, through and through.
He doesn't know how we
do things within the walls.
Don't you worry about the Interior Police.
We won't write anything about 'em.
That goes for their new ODM gear, too.
I appreciate it, Roy.
Their new ODM gear...
That buckshot is useless against Titans,
but it's perfect for killing people.
It's a weapon practically made
for killing the Scouts...
Plus, its existence being hidden
even from us means...
...sooner or later, we might
find ourselves staring down
their muzzles all the same.
Anyways, we should hear a report
from them soon, so be patient.
Wait up, you fat-ass!
You idiot! That way's a dead end!
Shit!
Shit, he's gone!
Find him! Find him!
Don't let 'em escape!
You're the son of Boss Reeves, right?
What's your name?
Flegel.
Nice to meet you, Flegel.
I'm Hange Zoe.
The thing is, if the Military
Police is after you,
that must mean you know the truth
about your father's death, right?
Can you tell me what happened?
While I was busy taking a piss,
the Interior Police got my old man.
A tall guy wearing a black coat...
he killed my father.
In any case, it's great
that you're still alive.
Now we can make the truth public.
How's that?! Haven't you seen the paper?!
If the Military Police say the
Scouts did it, that's the truth!
My testimony means jack shit!
They know I was there... The Interior
Police found out I saw everything...
Now there's nowhere safe for me to go.
All I can do is run and hide
in these cramped walls...
My life is... shit!
Well, you have a point...
The thing is, that doesn't
sound like living to me.
Look at it this way, Flegel.
Instead of scampering around like
a scared little mouse your whole life,
wouldn't you rather face up to your enemy,
even if it means risking your life...?
Like hell I would!
Not everyone has the same disregard
for their lives as you do!
Not only that, but you have
no right to criticize me either!
Don't you care about telling your
company and family the truth?!
Huh?! That's just what's best for you!
Of course it is!
You oughta start thinking
what's best for you, too!
Who's that?! Who's making
a scene on my roof?!
Now then, you're coming with me, Flegel.
Hell no! Your gang already lost!
You've been defeated!
What are you talking about?
Defeat is all the Scout
Regiment has ever known!
Disguise as Military Police
to get by the guards...
Then figure out where Eren
was taken by snooping around.
To think we'd have no better option...
We just don't have time...
We've got no choice but to do or die.
Captain.
Now then...
Stohess District Military Police.
Private Marlo Freudenberg.
Captain Levi! It's really him!
Same assignment, Private Hitch Dreyse.
As for how we'll dispose of you...
Because of you guys, over 100 people
from Stohess District were killed!
Huh?
Hey!
You people... You might think
that you're all heroes of justice,
but the victims and their families
were dropped straight into hell!
Yeah, I know.
You there... You're from the
Southern Cadet Corps, yeah?
Just like Annie Leonhart.
Were you friends of hers?
No... I doubt she had any friends.
Being as gloomy and aloof as she was.
It's like she was a kid
afraid of other people...
I never got the chance to
know anything about her.
And the reason they still
haven't found her...
...is because she was pulverized
by a Titan into a puddle of jelly!
No...
Because the Titan in hiding was...
Annie Leonhart herself.
Goddammit, it makes me sick.
Nobody knows a damn thing about
this world... Not us or anyone else.
Except for those bastards
at the center of it all.
We'll release you both
as soon as we get out of here.
Annie was...
Captain Levi! Please let me help you!
I don't think what you
guys are doing is wrong!
If I can help correct this world's
injustice, I'll do whatever it takes!
What's with this guy?
I beg of you, Captain Levi!
Not a chance.
I can't tell how prepared you are about
making an enemy of the government.
Let's go.
Sasha. Tie them up somewhere nearby.
Yes, sir!
Captain.
Please let me do it.
Knock yourself out.
Stop.
We'll forget what we saw here.
Yeah, you will! Because both
of you will die here!
That's not what he said!
Letting you two run free is too dangerous.
I'll take it upon myself to kill you!
Please, believe us!
We know you guys are fighting
to try and save humanity!
Right, Hitch?!
Mmm, mmm!
As if I could trust you.
Especially you, Mr. Bowl Cut.
Who in their right mind
would cut their hair like that?
You'll get no sympathy from this guy!
Hitch, run!
My gun is faster, you know.
Wanna take your chances?
Your knife and my gun... Let's race!
Wait! I'm really your ally!
Why the hell would anyone
believe you'd wanna join us?
We're so severely outmatched,
you really think we can save humanity?
Then, why are you...?
Why are you still with the Scouts then?
I picked the wrong regiment to join.
As long as you guys have it in you
to risk your lives and keep fighting...
...I will trust you.
Hitch!
You damn horse face!
Wait, Hitch! He was just testing us!
Huh?!
Hey, you.
What would you have done
if I swung the knife at you?
Why did you trust me so much?
Somehow or another,
you remind me of a guy that I hate.
A damn idiot.
This idiot... Is it the same
one Annie talked about?
Hell if I know.
Everyone's an idiot.
Fortunately, we're both just as dumb.
Marlo, I think you proved your dedication.
That should be enough
to convince Captain Levi.
We're counting on you.
That over there is the least
manned checkpoint around.
All right. We'll handle it ourselves.
Get back to your squad
before it's suspicious.
Yes, sir.
Marlo, Hitch.
We're grateful.
Sir!
Let's go!
It's our turn to pick a fight!
Hmm?
It's me.
Captain, he's...
With the Interior Police.
I've got a few questions for him.
Let's move.
How dumb can you be?
Running into a deserted dump like this...
Shit!
But I owe you one, Flegel Reeves.
When you got away and
gave us the slip, I really...
I thought I was screwed!
For a minute there, I
thought they'd kill me.
Nice knowing you, Flegel. Thanks a bunch!
Ah, wait!
Why was my old man killed?!
Did the Interior Police do it?!
Huh? What does it matter to you?
You're about to be fresh corpse.
I-I wanna know before I die!
What did he ever do to
deserve being killed?!
Eh? You don't know?
He betrayed us and sided
with those damn Scouts.
Betrayed?
So you're saying it was the Interior
Police that made him kidnap those Scouts?!
Except it was a different squad than us.
Guess he didn't say a damn thing.
Not to his dimwit son.
And what if he would've refused?
Well, he'd have known a bit too much,
so he would've had to die.
What a fool.
Look where caring for the city
and workers got 'em.
You would never understand.
Hmm?
Talking like you're smart shit...
My old man taught me something.
That merchants gotta follow their nose.
And I'm damn glad that I did.
Because I found the people
who could avenge my old man!
And I side with them!
What's the matter, Flegel? Go on and
oink like a pig to be slaughtered!
You had your time, but it's over!
Look above you, morons!
Ouch!
Section Commander! You're too wild!
Hell yeah! Did you hear that, everyone?!
The... Scout Regiment...? Why?
Not so deserted, eh?
Perhaps it looks that way to you.
But, sorry.
I know it doesn't look like much,
but we still live here.
We heard everything.
The Interior Police and their schemes...
Everyone here is a witness.
S-So, what does it matter?
It's the government that
decides what's the truth!
You fools... Don't think you can
do this and get away with it!
You're all in for a world of hu...
Everyone... Don't worry.
The Reeves Company will protect this city.
As of today, I, Flegel Reeves...
I'm the boss.
So... from now... you can count... on me.
We're counting on you, Boss.
Speak up, man!
Congrats on the job.
Keep an eye on these Interior Police.
Right.
Stop it...
Where are Eren and Christa?
Oh, you're so brave.
That checkpoint back
there was just recruits
who could barely
wipe their own ass.
You think you're some sort of hero,
beating them down?
What an atrocious thing we've done.
But what's more atrocious
is this mouth of yours.
I recommend you start talking
while you're still able to use it.
Where are Eren and Christa?
It's no use!
All that's left for you now is
to run and hide inside these
walls, covered in mud and shit!
If you don't turn yourselves in, every
last Scout we captured will get the noose!
Starting with the one most
guilty of all, Erwin Smith!
Shut up.
That's for not answering my question.
Some Scouts' lives are
more valuable than others.
Only those dumb enough
to acknowledge that join us.
Tell me where Eren and Christa are at.
I-I don't know!
I'm not allowed to know!
Kenny Ackermann is a very cautious man!
Ackermann?
I know Kenny... Is that his last name?
It is, but...
True, there's a lot of things he doesn't
divulge... Especially the important stuff.
But you must have a rough idea.
You best try to remember.
...Stop it!
...You still have plenty of bones
left to break. ...Stop it!
...You still have plenty
of bones left to break.
You... You're insane!
Maybe I am.
Someone's coming from that way!
More than one!
Told you so, Captain.
It's no use.
One way or another, the Scouts
will soon come to an end!
I've seen you in better shape.
And to think you were
lecturing me the other day.
You're getting an audience with the King.
They'll decide how to dismantle the Scouts
and announce your final sentence.
Nile, huh?
Where was your house?
Stohess District, was it?
Is Marie...? Is your family doing well?
They're doing fine. Both
Marie and the kids.
I haven't been home in a while, but...
...it's around Eastern Wall Rose.
I see...
What's with the odd questions?
I entrusted something to Commander Pyxis.
When, and if the time comes...
When it comes, I will only watch.
It's up to you to decide. You... and them.
So, I take it not much
came out of Erwin in the end.
Indeed... He must not have learned
any secrets from Pastor Nick.
Historia Reiss can make all the
claims she wants about her name,
but they'll amount to nothing.
How silly.
In any case, they're all nothing
more than birds in a cage.
Just waiting to die...
Excuse me.
Erwin Smith has arrived.
Very well. We're coming.
Once we finally execute him,
all will be according to plan.
And just like they always have,
the wall's secrets will stay safe.
We'll protect the peace within the walls.
Forever...
Erwin.
Do you have any last words?
In order to protect the kingdom...
In order to protect the King,
they kept the truth hidden.
However, in doing so, they invite
an uprising of the people.
Next Episode: "Reply."
"Reply"